8 days to go.
Who's back in the games?
They're going to be back with deliveries here,
dummy.
The camera is dirty.
The car had been broken for three days,
orders were delayed,
so you have to honor it.
You know,
now I have to run with the deliveries.
Fire in the playground.
Why can't you be warm now,
uncle?
It was here that they asked for the concept.
Then, guys,
I'm with Juliana.
I came for the repair.
Oh,
you don't understand anything.
That's what I love for you.
I can't take this love strawberry anymore,
bro.
Everywhere I have 1 financier here,
here they asked for 8 cashiers,
it's on,
you have to go up to deliver this,
bro,
to warn that the is not up.
I have that little box because it's cheaper.
And then there was the embezzlement of the chevas.
And the idea is to make some money,
ask for a few things in the graphic,
but I need a little box more than an hour,
because this one doesn't generate as much value.
So from the brand came the art of chevas and I wanted to show you
little box here you like,
thanks.
I just sold ten little coffins from a hundred and fifty.
The guy po,
I sent you there,
then I went to confirm the pix two hundred,
so I said bro it's two hundred,
isn't that right,
bro?
I won fifty old tale.
The deliveries are working.
Now I also need to invest in inputs to be able
to produce and think of another strategic plan,
because from now on it's marketing.
Stitch.
I'm not going to leave the chevas and I'm
going to do my best to get out of this situation.
There I get stagnant in this money.
Disassemble 1 deal,
show you 1 thing
ルMax.
Now you're going to see what it's like to appeal in marketing.